A Guide to the Fairfax County Office of Public Affairs Photograph Collection, 1962-2009
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Series 7: CD-ROMs, 2001-2008
  - CD-ROM, Richmond Visit 2-9-2006, Individual Digital File Folders: Comittees; Luncheon; News Conference; People; Staff [2 copies], 2006 February 9 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - CD-ROM, Individual Digital File Folders: Pietsch; Sneak Peek; South Center; Sully Opening; Tax Food Judging; West Nile, 2006 April-June (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - CD-ROM, Individual Digital File Folders: Attorneys 5-11-06; Bike to Work Day 5-19-06; DPWES Picnic 5-17-06; DTA Bake Competition; DTA Food 5-8-06; DTA Picnic 5-5-06; Earth Day 4-21-06; ERICA Award 5-4-06; Hanley Shelter 4-23-06; Juvenile Court Awards; Karate 5-10-06; Katrina 4-28-06; Lorton Landfill 5-9-06; Millennium Whelan.; Oakton Library 4-8-06; Parc Reston 5-5-06; Window Replacement 5-13-06; Window wash 4-13-06, 2006 April 8-May 19 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - CD-ROM, Individual Digital File Folders: Attorneys 5-11-06; Bike to Work Day 5-19-06; Business Flu Summit 5-26-06; Court House 4-19-06; ERICA Award 5-4-06; Hanley Shelter 4-23-06; Jump & Pump 4-11-06; Lisa Connors 5-18-06; Parc Reston 5-5-06; Photo Contest 5-26-06; Window Repair 5-13-06; Window washer 4-13-06, 2006 April-May (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - CD-ROM, Slain Police Officers Vicky O. Armel and Michel E. Garbarino Funeral Procession, Individual Digital File Folders: F.C.P. Mem, 2006 May (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - CD-ROM, Individual Digital File Folders: Angie Carrera 1-15-06; Animal Shelter 9-06; Board group 11-21-05; Business Flue Summit 5-26-06; County Carolers 12-6-06; Courthouse 4-19-06; DAHS 10-03-06; DCCCP 12-06; Debt Managers 9-19-06; DHR DOF lunch 10-30-06; Disability Delegation; DTA 10-4-06; DTA Witches 10-31-06, 2006 May-December (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - CD-ROM, Individual Digital File Folders: Edison Shelter 6-27-06; Employee Awards 7-21-06; Employee Awards 11-17-06; Fire&Rescue Equipment 8-18-06; Health Dept. Awards 12-07-06; Holiday Food Drive 12-13-06; Jack Herrity Event 6-12-06; John Frey 9-14-06; Katheryn Micky and Sonia Skipper 8-25-06; Logos; Millennium Forum 09-27-06; Millennium Forum 12-04-06; Neighborhood College 11-03-06; Pohick Library 6-8-06, 2006 May-December (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - CD-ROM, Individual Digital File Folders: Links; Retire Gifts 12-19-06; Rohr Brothers 8-18-06; SACC Orientation; Santa's Ride 12-13-06; Security Awareness 10-20-06; Station 40 Dedication 07-08-06; TAP Profiles 8-06; Top Off AEOC 6-21-06; Vehicle Rally 6-16-06; Volunteer Fest 10-28-06; Youth Survey HS panel 10-18-06, 2006 May-December (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - CD-ROM, Santa's Ride, Individual Digital File Folder: Santa's Ride 12-13-06, 2006 December 13 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - CD-ROMs, Huntington Cleanup [5 discs], 2006 June 30 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - CD-ROM, Burke Centre Library and Burke VRE Parking Garage Groundbreakings, Individual Digital File Folder: Burke Groundbreaking 7-29-06, 2006 July (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - CD-ROM, Courier Photos, Individual Digital File Folders: ART Conference 4-20-07; Bethany Timmes 2-7-07; Bicycle Coordinator 5-2-07; Celebrate Fairfax 6-8-07; Consumer Affairs 2-9-07; County Carolers 12-6-06; DFS Awards 5-9-07; DPZ present Co. Atty; DVS Award 7-12-07; EAC 5-10-07; Earth Day Expo 4-20-07; Employee Awards 11-17-06; Employee Fitness Tips; Health Dept. Awards 12-07-06; Holiday Food Drive 12-13-06; Lee Raine 1-24-07; Logos; Millennium Forum 3-28-07; Millennium Forum 12-04-06; Norm Graves 6-25-07; Retire Gifts 12-19-06; Retirement Agency 1-03-07; Santa's Ride 12-13-06; Watch Officers 1-04-07; Watch Officers (2) 1-09-07, 2006 December-2007 July (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - CD-ROMs, Courier Archives, 2007 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - CD-ROM, Individual Digital File Folders: Bethany Timmes 2-7-07; Consumer Affairs 2-9-07; Gang Prevention 2-9-07; Lee Rainie 1-24-07; Retirement Agency 1-03-07; Watch Officers (2) 1-09-07; Watch Officers 1-04-07; Youth Leadership 1-24-07, 2007 January-February (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - CD-ROM, BOS Meetings Presentation Photos, Individual Digital File Folders: Board 1-8-07; Board 1-22-07; Board 2-5-07; Board 2-26-07; Board 3-12-07; Board 3-26-07, 2007 January-March (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - CD-ROM, Individual Digital File Folders: ART Conference 4-20-07; Earth Day Expo 4-20-07; Gov. Kaine Visit 3-7-07; Kids to Work Day 4-26-07; Millennium Forum 3-28-07; OPA Awards 3-23-07; Virginia Tech Tragedy 4-18-07, 2007 March-April (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - CD-ROM, BOS Meetings Presentation Photos, Individual Digital File Folders: Board 4-9-07; Board 4-23-07; Board 4-30-07; Board 5-7-07; Board 5-21-07; Board 6-4-07; Board 6-18-07, 2007 April-June (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - CD-ROMs, National Public Safety Telecommunications Week Press Conference [2 discs], 2007 April 5 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - CD-ROM, HR People, Individual Digital File Folders: Animal Shelter 5-07; Archana Chhaya Library 5-07; Darryl Edwards VS 5-07; Eugene Huggins Animal Shelter 5-07; Florence Rowland CEX 5-07; Greg Licamele OPA 5-07; Joe Briggs DTA 5-07; Lupe Guerrero Health 5-07; Mai Vu CRS 5-07; MPO Burkiss Smith Duo Police 5-07; MPO Chris Burkiss Police 5-07; MPO Tracy Smith Police 5-07; Reginal Johnson F&R 5-07; Stacey Kincaid Sheriff 5-07; Tom Cutler DPWES 5-07; Tonya Saules SACC 5-07; Wang Bank Parks 5-07, 2007 May (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - CD-ROM, Individual Digital File Folders: Bicycle Coordinator 5-2-07; DFS Awards 5-9-07; DPWES 5-22-07; DPWES Picnic 5-24-07; DTA Bake Off 5-14-07; DVS Award 7-12-07; EAC 5-10-07; Employee awards 7-27-07; Michael Liberman 7-23-07; Norm Graves 6-25-07; Strike Team Press Conf 6-8-07, 2007 May-July (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - CD-ROM, BOS Meetings Presentation Photos, Individual Digital File Folders: Board 7-9-07; Board 7-23-07; Board 8-6-07; Board 9-10-07; Board 9-24-07; Board 10-15-07; Board 11-19-07; Board 12-3-07, 2007 July-December (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - CD-ROM, Kathrine K. Hanley Family Shelter, Individual Digital File Folders: Shelter Breakfast 7-17-07; Shelter Facility 7-17-07; Shelter Outside 7-21-07, 2007 July (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - CD-ROM, Kathrine K. Hanley Family Shelter Ribbon Cutting Ceremony, 2007 August 4 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - CD-ROM, Individual Digital File Folders: Connector Bus 10-15-07; Creative economies 10-25-07; DPWES 10-2-07; Emergency Response Open House 9-19-07; Millennium Forum 9-26-07; Park Authority All Hands 9-20-07; Probation 9-30-05; SMT Ethics Mtg 9-19-07, 2007 September-October (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - CD-ROM, Oakton Library Opening Day, 2007 September 29 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - CD-ROM, Individual Digital File Folders: GIS Day 11-14-07; Inauguration 2007; Leadership Meeting 12-14-07; Millennium Forum 11-28-07; OPA Awards 12-10-07; Santa and Elves 12-12-07; Set Up Inauguration 07, 2007 November-December (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - CD-ROM, Photographs of Fairfax County Inauguration Ceremony, Len Spoden Photography, 2007 December 12 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - CD-ROM, 9/11 Memorial Grove Ceremony, Individual Digital File Folder: 911.Ceremony 9.8.08, 2008 September 8 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - CD-ROM, Governors Visit Fire Academy, Individual Digital File Folder: Vaf1.Governors.Visit.10.08, 2008 October (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - CD-ROM, McConnel Public Safety and Transportation Operations Center (MPSTOC) Dedication [2 discs], 2008 October 10 (Box 33, Folder 27)
- Series 8: Original Indexes, 1971-1993
  - 1964-1971 Index to Negative Files, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - 1975-1977 Card Index to Photo Negatives [contained in metal box], 1975-1977 (Box 34)
  - 1987-1993 List of Photographs Taken, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Series 9: Slides, 1964-1998
  - Aerial Views, 1968-1969 (Box 35)
  - Amhurst Overpass - Springfield, 1985 (Box 35)
  - Apartment and Subdivision Development - Londontowne/Reston, 1970 (Box 35)
  - Board of Supervisors, 1984-1998 (Box 35)
  - Bond Referendum - 1980 Fall Slide Show - November 4, 1980, 1980 (Box 35)
  - Bond Referendum - 1984 Fall Slide Show, 1984 (Box 35)
  - Bond Referendum - 1984 Slide Show, 1984 (Box 35)
  - Bond Referendum - 1985 Slide Show, 1985 (Box 35)
  - Bond Referendum - 1988 Spring Slide Show - April 12, 1988, 1988 (Box 35)
  - Bond Referendum - 1988 Fall Slide Show, 1988 (Box 35)
  - Bond Referendum - 1989 Fall Slide Show - November 7, 1989, 1989 (Box 35)
  - Bond Referendum - 1990 Fall Slide Show - November 6, 1990, 1990 (Box 35)
  - Bond Referendum - 1992 Fall Slide Show - November 2, 1992, 1992 (Box 36)
  - Bond Referendum - 1992 Site/Transportation, 1992 (Box 36)
  - Child Protective Services, 1977 (Box 36)
  - City of Alexandria, 1969-1970 (Box 36)
  - Construction, 1969-1988 (Box 36)
  - Corporate Park at Government Center, 1991 (Box 36)
  - County Executive - J. Hamilton Lambert - August 1988, 1988 (Box 36)
  - County Executive - J. Hamilton Lambert - 1986 American Heart Association "Cardiac Arrest", 1986 (Box 36)
  - County Facilities - Miscellaneous, 1968-1981 (Box 36)
  - County Seal, 1985 (Box 36)
  - Courthouse Slide Show, 1977 (Box 36)
  - Crossroad's Association / Washington-Virginia Airport Site, 1970 (Box 36)
  - Crystal City / Shirlington, 1968-1970 (Box 36)
  - Department of Recreation, 1970 (Box 36)
  - Dulles Airport, 1968-1970 (Box 36)
  - Fairfax Connector Buses, 1985 (Box 36)
  - Fire Service / Police Substation, 1967 (Box 36)
  - Fort Belvoir, 1970 (Box 36)
  - Great Falls / C&O Canal, 1970 (Box 36)
  - Gum Springs and Mudtown, 1964-1969 (Box 36)
  - Health Services, 1969-1970 (Box 36)
  - Herndon Station, 1970 (Box 36)
  - Historic Scenes, 1970 (Box 36)
  - History of Fairfax County Slide Show, 1982 (Box 36)
  - Industrial Parks and Virginia Gentleman, 1970 (Box 36)
  - Jail Slide Show (Bond Referendum), 1981 (Box 36)
  - Lake Braddock, 1970 (Box 37)
  - Library, 1980 (Box 37)
  - Library Headquarters / George Mason Regional Library (Annandale), 1969 (Box 37)
  - Lower Potomac Treatment Plant and Sewer Construction, 1970 (Box 37)
  - Maps of Fairfax County, 1980 (Box 37)
  - Metro - Opening of Vienna Metro Station - June 7, 1986, 1986 (Box 37)
  - Northern Virginia Community College, 1970 (Box 37)
  - Old Courthouse, 1977 (Box 37)
  - Planning Commission - November 1984, 1984 (Box 37)
  - Reston, 1970 (Box 37)
  - Road and Traffic Scenes, 1970-1985 (Box 37)
  - Rosslyn, 1969-1970 (Box 37)
  - Rural Shots, 1970 (Box 37)
  - Scenic pictures around the county, 1969-1980 (Box 37)
  - Schools, 1969-1970 (Box 37)
  - Shoney's Inn - Tysons, 1985 (Box 37)
  - Shopping Centers and Commercial Development, 1968-1970 (Box 37)
  - Storm Drainage Improvement, 1980 (Box 37)
  - Tank Farm Spill, Undated (Box 37)
  - Vienna Station, 1970 (Box 37)
  - "Voters Have Pull", 1984 (Box 37)
  - Warrants and Files - Courthouse, 1977 (Box 37)
- Series 10: Photographs, 1963-2009
  - Aerial Views, 1968-1976 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Animal Control, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Area Agency on Aging, Undated (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Board of Supervisors, 1971-2008 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Board of Supervisors - Sharon Bulova, 1988-2008 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Board of Supervisors - Tom Davis, Undated (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Board of Supervisors - Robert B. Dix, Jr., Undated (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Board of Supervisors - John Foust, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Board of Supervisors - Michael Frey, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Board of Supervisors - Katherine Hanley, Undated (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Board of Supervisors - John F. "Jack" Herrity, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Board of Supervisors - Pat Herrity, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Board of Supervisors - Gerald W. "Gerry" Hyland, 1994-2008 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Board of Supervisors - Charles Majer, Undated (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Board of Supervisors - Jeff McKay, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Board of Supervisors - Audrey Moore, Undated (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Board of Supervisors - Lilla Richards, Undated (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Board of Supervisors - James "Jim" Scott, Undated (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Board of Supervisors - Linda Smyth, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Board of Supervisors - Christine R. Trapnell, Undated (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Board of Supervisors - Marie B. Travesky, Undated (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Board of Supervisors - Anne Wilkins, Undated (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Board of Zoning Appeals, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Construction, 1968-1970 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Consumer Affairs, 1975-1977 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Cooperative Extension, 1975-1976 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - County Executive - First County Executive Interns, 1998 November (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - County Executive - Anthony H. Griffin, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - County Executive - Gilda Harris, Undated (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - County Executive - Mary Elizabeth Holbein, Undated (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - County Executive - Richard A. King, Undated (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - County Executive - J. Hamilton Lambert, 1985-1998 (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - County Executive - William J. Leidinger, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - County Executive - Carlton. C. Massey, 1966-1982 (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - Courts, 1967-1989 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Data Systems, Undated (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Deputy County Executive - Verdia Haywood, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Deputy County Executive - Denton V. Kent, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Deputy County Executive - Edward L. Long Jr., Undated (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Deputy County Executive - James P. McDonald, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Dulles Airport, Undated (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Equipment Management Transportation Agency - (EMTA), 1976 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Environment Management (EQAC), 1965-1978 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Fire Department, 1968-1984 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Fire Department - Awards & Presentations, 1970-1991 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Fire Department - Fire Stations, 1967-1985 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Government Center, 1982-1992 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Government Center - 9/11 Memorial Grove Dedication Ceremony, 2003 September 15 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Government Center - Herrity/Pennino Dedication Ceremony, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Governmental Center - Mason, Undated (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Governmental Center - Mount Vernon, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Governmental Center - North County, Undated (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Governmental Center - West Springfield, Undated (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Health Department, 1967-1976 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Historical Pictures - History Book Publications, 1973-1988 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Historical Pictures - History Commission, Undated (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Historical Pictures - Virginia Bicentennial, 1975-1976 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Home Economics, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - International Delegation Visits, 2006-2009 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Libraries, 1969-1984 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Maps, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Massey Building, 1967-1968 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Metro, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Metro - Huntington Metro, 1990-1991 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Office of Public Affairs, Undated (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Office of Public Affairs - Jennifer Bassarab, Undated (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Office of Public Affairs - Debra Bianchi, Undated (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Office of Public Affairs - Tom Clark, Undated (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Office of Public Affairs - Linda Crone, Undated (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Office of Public Affairs - Cari Dellinger, Undated (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Office of Public Affairs - Maria Foltz, Undated (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Office of Public Affairs - Ebony Grant, Undated (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Office of Public Affairs - Paula Harper, Undated (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Office of Public Affairs - Cathy Lemmon, Undated (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Office of Public Affairs - Bill Miller, Undated (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Office of Public Affairs - Angela Morlu, Undated (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Office of Public Affairs - Kathy Simmons, Undated (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Office of Public Affairs - Melissa Smith, Undated (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Office of Public Affairs - Amarjit Sodhi, Undated (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Office of Public Affairs - Dorothy Stangl, Undated (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Park Authority, 1967-1983 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Park Authority - Burke Lake Park, 1963-1969 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Park Authority - Colvin Run Mill, Undated (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Park Authority - Lake Accotink, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Park Authority - Lake Fairfax, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Park Authority - Northern Virginia Regional Park Authority, 1963-1976 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Print Shop, Undated (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Recreation, 1967-1977 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Redskins Super Bowl Championship Parade, 1983? 1988? (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - School Board, 1972-1975 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Schools, 1967-1974 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Transportation, Undated (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Transportation - Blake Lane Ribboncutting, Undated (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Transportation - Nutley Road Ribboncutting (Cyril Katzen), ca. 2000 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Transportation - Wiehle Avenue Ribboncutting, Undated (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Unidentified - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Oversize Portraits of Board of Supervisors and others [contact sheets and negatives], Undated (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Series 11: Office of Public Affairs Employee Magnetic Photo Albums, c. 1970s-2000
  - [Brown] Magnetic Photo Album, c. 1970s-1984 (Box 42)
  - [Purple] Magnetic Photo Album, 1982-1998 [bulk 1992-1994] (Box 42)
  - [Blue] Magnetic Photo Album “Election Night”, November 8, 1983 Photos by Pam Rutkowski, 1983 November 8 (Box 43)
  - [Red] Magnetic Photo Album,, 1984-1998 (Box 43)
  - [Green] Magnetic Photo Album, 1989-1999 (Box 44)
  - [Blue-marbled] Magnetic Photo Album, c. 1991-2000 (Box 44)